Guillermo Del Pino

Santiago, RM \mid (+56) 95600 4443 \mid g.delpino@outlook.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/gdelpinocastro/

I have experience as an intern at the market risk department of Santander Chile. Additionally, I have worked as a support lecturer at Adolfo Ibáñez University in subjects such as Calculus and Algebra. I have knowledge of various programming tools, specifically focused on implementing financial models. In addition to expertise in quantitative finance subjects such as stochastic calculus, option pricing, fixed-income derivatives, exotic options, among others.

Work Experience

SANTANDER

Market & Capital Risk Internship – (Aug. 2023- Nov. 2023)

MARIA BOOTH

E-commerce support and Online Marketing—(Nov. 2022- Feb. 2023)

ADOLFO IBAÑEZ UNIVERSITY

Teaching Assistant: Algebra I– (2020) Teaching Assistant: Calculus I– (2020)

Teaching Assistant: Argumentative Writing—(2021)

Education

ADOLFO IBAÑEZ UNIVERSITY Master of Financial Engineering – (2023-2024)

Dynamic Asset Allocation Exotic Derivative Pricing Fixed-Income Derivatives Stochastic Calculus

ADOLFO IBAÑEZ UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's degree in economics -(2019 - 2023)

Econometrics

Microeconomics, Macroeconomics

Courses & Certifications

BLOOMBERG LP – BLOOMBERG MARKET CONCEPTS

December 2023

BLOOMBERG LP - BLOOMBERG MARKET CONCEPTS

June 2022

UC BERKELEY – GLOBAL LEADERSHIP & INNOVATION VIRTUAL PROGRAM

January 2021

Technical Skills

Bloomberg Terminal

Basic

MS Excel

Intermediate

Programming Languages

Matlab, R, Python, VBA

Query Languages

SQL (basic)

Languages

Spanish (Native) English (Advanced)